{
    "tags": "umbraco umbraco7 grid layout gridlayout",
    "idprefix": "umbraco7.grid",
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "What CSS Grid system is used in Grid Layout?",
            "answer": "Bootstrap 3 Grid system.",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "How many columns Bootstrap Grid Layout has by default?",
            "answer": "12",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "question": "How to define overall Grid Layout?",
            "answer": "In Data Type add Grid Layout for whole grid layout property.",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 40,
            "question": "How to restrict available editors for a row configuration?",
            "answer": "Row Configuration -> Menu -> Select available editor.",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 50,
            "question": "What are cells in row definition and how many of them you can create?",
            "answer": "Cells are the definitons of layout of row definitin, what editors are available in each cell and the width of each cell. There can be a lot of cells in row definiton.",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 60,
            "question": "Where do you create Grid layout ?",
            "answer": "grid Layouts are created in Developer Section of Umbraco BackOffice.",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "80",
            "question": "How many editors can Grid Layout cell have inside ?",
            "answer": "One or more editors.",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "90",
            "question": "How the grid is stored in database?",
            "answer": "a json document with all settings and data",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "110",
            "question": "How to render grid layout?",
            "answer": "<pre>@CurrentPage.GetGridHtml(\"<propertyName>\")</pre>",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "120",
            "question": "How to render grid layout with diffrent renderer?",
            "answer": "<pre>@CurrentPage.GetGridHtml(\"<propertyName>\", \"<nameOfCssGridFramework_eg_Bootstrap3>\")</pre>",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "130",
            "question": "Where to create the template for custom Grid layout?",
            "answer": "Settings -> Partial Views -> Grid -> Create Template.",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "140",
            "question": "Where should you put custom GridEditor?",
            "answer": "In package.manifest in /App_plugins/my_folder/",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "150",
            "question": "What wil hapend if you render grid layout property with @Umbraco.Field(\"gridLayoutProperty\")?",
            "answer": "The grid layout data json will be rendered",
            "tags": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "160",
            "question": "Where do you configure Settings and Styles?",
            "answer": "In the content editor.",
            "tags": ""
        }
    ]
}
